[{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980120103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":22786,"timeElapsed":70916},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980129540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9435,"timeElapsed":80353},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980133581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4039,"timeElapsed":84394},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980137374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3790,"timeElapsed":88186},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980140560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3184,"timeElapsed":91373},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980145789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5227,"timeElapsed":96602},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980154602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8811,"timeElapsed":105415},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980161686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7082,"timeElapsed":112499},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980164518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2830,"timeElapsed":115331},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980224053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":58314,"timeElapsed":174866},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980235259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":11204,"timeElapsed":186071},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980237853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2593,"timeElapsed":188666},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980248330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":10476,"timeElapsed":199143},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980253971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5639,"timeElapsed":204784},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980260023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6051,"timeElapsed":210836},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980277342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":17317,"timeElapsed":228155},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980281016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3672,"timeElapsed":231828},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980287795,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6777,"timeElapsed":238608},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980296256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"179","question":"What is your favorite US city to visit? If you live outside the United States, do you have a favorite city to visit in your own country?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":8459,"timeElapsed":247068},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980308999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":9887,"timeElapsed":259812},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980317809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8809,"timeElapsed":268622},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":10264,"timeElapsed":278888},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980336610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8533,"timeElapsed":287423},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4952,"timeElapsed":292376},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":21584,"timeElapsed":313961},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980392672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":29522,"timeElapsed":343485},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5511,"timeElapsed":348997},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":11000,"timeElapsed":359999},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6788,"timeElapsed":368015},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13154,"timeElapsed":381171},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2548,"timeElapsed":383721},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2481,"timeElapsed":386203},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6521,"timeElapsed":392727},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4777,"timeElapsed":397506},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4132,"timeElapsed":401639},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3584,"timeElapsed":405224},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3599,"timeElapsed":408825},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8525,"timeElapsed":418528},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":11082,"timeElapsed":429612},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4058,"timeElapsed":433672},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980485736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2876,"timeElapsed":436549},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4778,"timeElapsed":441328},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":9184,"timeElapsed":450513},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":453881},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4885,"timeElapsed":458767},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3253,"timeElapsed":462022},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6113,"timeElapsed":469306},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4640,"timeElapsed":473947},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3448,"timeElapsed":477397},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980535630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":9045,"timeElapsed":486443},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4153,"timeElapsed":490597},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4108,"timeElapsed":494707},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8801,"timeElapsed":503510},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4983,"timeElapsed":508494},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4990,"timeElapsed":513485},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":23935,"timeElapsed":538728},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":89037,"timeElapsed":627767},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3936,"timeElapsed":631705},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3117,"timeElapsed":634823},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2768,"timeElapsed":637593},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4147,"timeElapsed":641742},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980693012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2081,"timeElapsed":643825},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3877,"timeElapsed":647704},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2752,"timeElapsed":650458},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4600,"timeElapsed":656006},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2687,"timeElapsed":658695},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2389,"timeElapsed":661084},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2247,"timeElapsed":663334},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3073,"timeElapsed":666408},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980718911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3314,"timeElapsed":669724},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3070,"timeElapsed":672796},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3030,"timeElapsed":675828},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":678026},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980814905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":86686,"timeElapsed":765718},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4448,"timeElapsed":770167},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980824610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5254,"timeElapsed":775423},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980830789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6177,"timeElapsed":781602},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3209,"timeElapsed":784813},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4603,"timeElapsed":789418},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980841770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3164,"timeElapsed":792583},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845191,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3419,"timeElapsed":796004},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3050,"timeElapsed":799055},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3006,"timeElapsed":802063},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":26354,"timeElapsed":830098},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3223,"timeElapsed":833322},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980885144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2633,"timeElapsed":835957},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3584,"timeElapsed":839542},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980892171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3440,"timeElapsed":842984},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980894992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":845804},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980897362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2369,"timeElapsed":848175},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980900886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3522,"timeElapsed":851699},{"subjectID":"dp65p4efq5","prolificID":"65b2bfa958c28d5efd353c4d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b269a9a4c98f1e3e7b66","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2617,"timeElapsed":854318}]